Who do you trust? The Bible or the
government? Does God still speak to
humanity like he used to in the Bible?
Admittedly, I wasn't paying enough
attention until something strange
happened the other day.
A flock of ravens circling my house got
my attention. That is absolutely wild.
Especially with the stuff going on in
Israel.
The crows shook me up a little bit, so I
pulled out the Bible to find instances
of [music] God speaking to humanity.
Genesis 8, chapter 12, and the dove came
in to an even tide and lo her mouth had
an olive plucked off of it. So, Noah
knew the waters were abated from off the
earth. God talked to Noah with a dove.
Genesis [music] chapter 22, verse 13,
Abraham lifted up his eyes and looked
and behold behind him a ram caught in
the thicket by his thorns. Abraham as
Jacob's grandpa God spoke to him with a
ram. God [music] has always spoken to
humanity using animals and natural
signs. And then there are a lot of
prophecies about it, too. Let's look in
the Old Testament. Joel chapter 2, verse
31, "The sun shall be turned to darkness
and the moon into blood before the great
and terrible day of the Lord come."
March 27, 2028, Australia, the entire
sky [music] turned blood red. Couple
days later, Greece, another blood red
sky. There was a blood moon seen in
[music] 23 countries on March 3, 2026.
Do you think these count as signs in the
heavens or are they easily explained by
a sandstorm and a hurricane? Who do you
trust? The Bible or the government? Luke
21:25, "There shall be signs in the sun
and in the moon and in the stars and
upon the earth distress of nations."
Anybody in any nation feeling any
distress right now? Now to the end times
prophecy, Revelation chapter 6, verse
13, "Stars of heaven fell into [music]
earth." How many balls of fire appeared
over America in the last week? It wasn't
one, it was like eight. Stars.
Revelation chapter 8, verse 10 and 11,
"There fell a great star from heaven
burning as if it were a lamp." I'm not
some crazy man telling you that the end
is near. I'm merely pointing at how God
spoke to humanity [music] in the Bible,
current events that I'm observing, and a
strange occurrence of crows around my
house. and I will leave you with the
words of [music] Jesus, and you shall
hear of wars and rumors of wars. All
these things must come to pass.
Are we living in the end times? I
[music] don't know. I'm just pointing
out observation and correlation.